ANTONIO MASA

Phone: 939-358-5611

E-mail: amasa89@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

A position where I can use my education, skills, and experience to benefit my employer and further my professional experience while maintaining quality and exceeding management expectations with honesty, integrity, and a strong work ethic.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Medical Technologist

May 2018- March 2019

Employer: Lab Corp, Weatherford, TX.

Manager: Jenelle Lee

Responsible for the processing of laboratory specimens in the following area: hematology and urinalysis.

Perform quality control, QC review, and troubleshooting, daily and weekly maintenance on a variety of equipment. Also run parallel in the area of hematology.

Medical Technologist

February 2018- April 2018

Employer: Urgent Care of Texas, Arlington, TX.

Manager: Than Luong.

Responsible for the processing of laboratory specimens in the following area: hematology, chemistry, urinalysis, serology and reference.

Perform quality control, QC review, and troubleshooting, daily and weekly maintenance on a variety of equipment.

Medical Technologist

February 2017-August 2017

Employer: Meditech3 Clinical Laboratory

Supervisor: Anabell Escanio, 787-948-6665; may be contacted.

Responsible for the processing of laboratory specimens in the following area: hematology, urinalysis, serology and reference.

Perform quality control, QC review, and troubleshooting, daily and weekly maintenance.

Perform serology (i.e. RPR, influenza and pregnancy test).

Perform phlebotomy.

Medical Technologist

June 2016 – August 2017

Employer: CESMI Clinical Laboratory, Bayamon, PR

Supervisor: Ana Santana, 787-380-9051; may be contacted.

Responsible for the processing of laboratory specimens in the following area: hematology, chemistry, urinalysis, serology and reference.

Perform quality control, QC review, and troubleshooting, daily and weekly maintenance on a variety of equipment.

Perform serology (i.e. RPR, influenza and pregnancy test). Maintain proficiency and competency testing evaluations in order. Perform phlebotomy.

Interpretations and reviews of laboratory results.

Medical Technologist/Per diem

May 2016- July 2017

Employer: (Edwin Cardona & Asoc.for the hospital: San Jorge Children Hospital), San Juan, PR

Supervisor: Jennifer Rivera, 787-364-0393; may be contacted.

Responsible for the processing of laboratory specimens in the following area: hematology, coagulation, blood bank, parasitology, urinalysis, serology and blood gas.

Perform quality control, QC review, and troubleshooting, daily maintenance on a variety of equipment.

Serology (e.i. influenza, RSV, mono virus and pregnancy test). Parasitology (i.e. occult blood, leucocyte count and rota virus test).

EDUCATION

2007-2012	Universidad Del Turabo, Gurabo, PR Department of Science and Technology
	Bachelor's Degree in Biology

2015-2016 Universidad Interamericana, Recinto Metropolitano, San Juan, PR Department of Medical Technology

Certification in Medical Laboratory Scientist

CERTIFICATES/LICENSES

2016- Present American Society of Clinical Pathologists (ASCP) Board of Registry Medical

Technologist License

Status: Active

2016- Present Puerto Rico Medical Technology Board of Medical Examiners Medical Technologist

License

Status: Inactive

PROFESSIONAL/ ORGANIZATIONS

2016- Present Member of College of Medical Technologist of Puerto Rico, Guaynabo, PR

COMPUTER SKILLS

Ability in Microsoft Word, Excel, Power Point and Outlook.

SCIENTIFIC ARTICLE

2012: A. Masa, J. Ducongé, M. Cotto, A. García, F. Márquez, *Photocatalytic hydrogen production by water splitting using novel catalysts under UV-vis light irradiation (Published)*.